英语语法之-将来完成时
将来完成时是以“将来”作为“坐标时间”
来表示开始于将来之前（可能是过去、现在或将来）的动作持续到将来
但动作开始的时间并不重要 关键是说话人要站在将来的某一时间来谈某一动作的完成情况
例句1）“我们”可能是昨天开始考试的 比如说成：
We started our exam yesterday and we will have taken five exams by next Friday.
例句2）可能是今天开始考试的 比如说成：
We have started our exam today and we will have taken five exams by next Friday.
例句3）也可能是明天才开始考试 比如说成：
We will start our exam tomorrow and we will have taken five exams by next Friday.
但具体是哪一天开始的并不重要 说话人强调的是他们一共有五门考试
将来完成时的三种思维用法
延续事件
表示在将来某一时刻之前开始的动作 一直延续到该时刻
并可能继续延续下去
I will have taught English in New Oriental School for five years by the end of next month.
到下个月底之前 我在新东方学校教英语的时间将满五年
I will have learned 8 000 words by the end of next year.
到明年年底之前 我将学会8 000个单词
重复事件
表示在将来的某一时刻之前开始的动作 并在该时刻之前的一段时间内重复发生
By five o clock this afternoon the spaceship will have traveled eleven times round the world.
到今天下午五点钟之前 这艘宇宙飞船就将绕地球飞行11次了
单一事件
表示在将来的某一时刻之前开始的动作 到该时刻之前已经完成
We will have finished our exam by the end of next
week.
到下个周末为止 我们将完成考试
By the year 2050 scientists probably will have discovered a cure
for cancer.
到2050年时 科学家可能会找到治愈癌症的方法
I will graduate in July.
I will see you in
September.
By the time I see you I will have graduated.
我将于7月份毕业 于9月份与你见面 到我见到你的时候 我就已经毕业了